ibeesoft.com 2018-06-30

# iBeesoft Privacy Policy

iBeesoft respects your privacy choices and is committed to protecting your privacy of the information you share with us.We just collect some neccessary information to complete purchase transactions and deliver our software.iBeesoft will not sell, distribute, or rent information about you and your purchase information to any third parties.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to [contact us](mailto:support@ibeesoft.com).

## What information we collect? What do we use it for?

When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, etc will be required. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you.

When you email to us, your email or name will be used for the communication between us.

## How We Use the Information We Collect

We uses secure server and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information.

iBeesoft collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and deliver the services or carry out the transactions you have requested. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. Some iBeesoft services, such as iBeesoft Newsletter, may send periodic member letters that are considered part of the service. We may also occasionally send you product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from iBeesoft and its affiliates.

Personal information collected on iBeesoft sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which iBeesoft or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using an iBeesoft site or service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. iBeesoft abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

## How We Protect the Information We Collect

iBeesoft is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We have implemented a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.

When we transmit highly confidential information over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layers (SSL) protocol.

iBeesoft will not sell, lease or rent its email subscriber lists to third parties. While iBeesoft continues to actively review and implement new technology, such as expanded filtering features, there is no currently available technology that will totally prevent the sending and receiving of unsolicited email. Using tools such as the Inbox Protector and being cautious about the sharing of your email address while online will help reduce the amount of unsolicited email you receive.
